分歧者：异类觉醒/分歧者:异类叛逃(港)/分歧者(台)
翻译&校对：jyopon
翻译&校对：networmii
OCR&校对&翻译：timhal
后期：timhal
HDWinG字幕组原创翻译作品  转载请勿去除译者信息
更多原创作品  请登录HDWinG.COM
(芝加哥)
我们为自己身在城中而感到幸运
We're lucky to be in The City.
他们说城外的战争惨不忍睹
They say the war was terrible,
城外的世界已支离破碎
that the rest of the world was destroyed.
创始者建造起围栏来保证我们的安全
Our founders built the wall to keep us safe
他们将我们分成五个不同的派系
and they divided us into five groups, factions,
以确保我们和睦相处
to keep the peace.
崇尚知识和逻辑的聪明人
The smart ones, the ones who value knowledge and logic
属于博学派
are in Erudite.
他们无所不知
They know everything.
友好派辛勤耕作
Amity farm the land.
他们都是善良和清静无为的人  永远充满欢乐
They're all about kindness and harmony, always happy.
诚实派崇尚诚信和秩序
Candor value honesty and order.
他们实话实说  即便你有时希望他们不要这样
They tell the truth, even when you wish they wouldn't.
接下来的派系是无畏派
And then there's Dauntless.
他们是城市的保护者、士兵以及警察
They're our protectors, our soldiers, our police.
我总是觉得他们十分神奇
I always thought they were amazing.
勇敢  无畏  无拘无束
Brave, fearless and free.
有些人觉得无畏派的人都是疯子
Some people think Dauntless are crazy,
不过他们也确实疯狂
which they kind of are.
过来  碧翠丝
Come on, Beatrice.
我的家庭是无私派的
My faction is Abnegation.
同龄的小孩都称呼我们为"呆子"
The others all call us "stiffs."
无私派家庭的孩子因为低调保守被同龄人调侃作"呆子"
我们过着十分简单的生活
We lead a simple life,
无私奉献  致力于帮助他人
selfless, dedicated to helping others.
我们甚至资助无派系的流浪者
We even feed the Factionless,
他们难以融入社会
the ones who don't fit in anywhere.
因为我们负责社会服务
Because we're public servants,
所以我们被人民所信任而成为执政派系
we're trusted to run the government.
我的父亲与我们无私派的领袖马库斯并肩作战
My father works alongside our leader, Marcus.
这样的派系区分十分有效  每个人都知道自己的归属
It all works. Everyone knows where they belong.
除了我
Except for me.
我妈妈说人有时会迷失自我
My mother says there's an art to losing yourself.
但是我不懂这话的含义
But I haven't figured it out yet.
她说人不该自私  只想着自己
I'm supposed to never think of myself,
而应该去帮助他人
to always help others.
不要长时间去看镜中的自己
To never look too long in the mirror.
你紧张吗
Are you nervous?
不
No.
你呢  你测试的时候紧张吗
Were you? For your test?
是的
Mmm-mmm. No.
我吓坏了
I was terrified.
但其实我并不需要害怕  你也不用
But I didn't have any reason to be and neither do you.
那都是你应得的
That's all you get.
规定就是规定
Rules are rules.
今天我要接受测试
Today I take the test.
我很害怕测试会说我不属于无私派
I'm scared it'll tell me I'm not Abnegation.
那样的话我就得离开我的家庭
That I have to leave my family.
但我更害怕它让我留下来
But I'm even more scared that it will tell me to stay.
对我的哥哥凯莱布来说  这不算什么
For my brother Caleb, it's easy.
让我来帮你拿吧
Let me help you with that.
他生来便是个无私的人
He's a natural.
碧翠丝  帮我拿下另外一个包好吗
Beatrice, do you wanna get the other bags?
不了
Sorry.
如果她是个盲人或残疾人
What if she'd been blind or an amputee?
你会去帮助她吗
Would you have helped her then?
我刚在想去帮助她的
I was thinking about helping her.
这又不是什么难事
It's not that hard.
对你来说也许不是
For you, maybe.
放轻松  碧翠丝  深呼吸然后相信测试就行了
Just relax, Beatrice. Take a deep breath and trust the test.
相信测试
Trust the test.
测试会告诉我我是谁  我的归属在哪个派系
Test will tell me who I am, where I belong.
我属于博学派吗
Am I smart?
友好派
Kind?
亦或是诚实派
Am I honest?
无私派
Selfless?
还是无畏派
Or brave?
嘿  那些我们得不到的食物
Hey. So, all the food that we're not getting,
你们都给流浪者了是吗
you guys are giving away to the Factionless?
-对吗    -是的
- Right? Yeah?  - Yeah.
你是个骗子  你为什么要骗我
You're a liar. Why are you lying to me?
谁都知道你们自己私吞了
Everybody knows you keep it for yourselves.
你们何不大方的承认呢
So why don't you just admit it?
听到没
Huh?
我在和你说话呢  你们这些呆子是聋的还是怎么了
I'm talking to you. Are all you stiffs deaf or somethin'? Hey!
碧翠丝
Beatrice...
不要
Don't.
一百年前  在战争结束后
One hundred years ago, after the war,
城市创始者创建了一套体制  他们相信这套体制可以防止未来的冲突
our founders created a system they believed would prevent future conflict
并且创造永久的和平
and create lasting peace.
今天  能力倾向测试将以你的性格为基准
Today, aptitude testing based on your personality
将你分配到相应的派系中去
will assign you to one of the factions.
我们相信用测试结果来决定派系
While it is our belief that choosing the faction
是当前派系制度下确保成功的
indicated by your test is the best way to ensure
最行之有效的方法
success within the faction system,
但你们也有权利在明天的选择仪式上
it is your right tomorrow at the choosing ceremony
撇开测试结果
to choose any of the five factions,
自行选择派系
regardless of your test results.
无论如何  一旦作出决定
However, once the choice has been made,
便不会再有更改选择的机会
there will be no change permitted.
听说你们无私派的人不怎么照镜子
What is it with you Abnegation and mirrors?
我们拒绝虚荣
We reject vanity.
我知道  坐下吧
Yeah. I know. Sit down.
我是托里  由我来对你进行测试
I'm Tori. I'll be administering your test.
你将会面对一系列的选择  来测试你适宜哪个派系
You'll be offered a series of choices to test your aptitude for each faction
直到得出结果为止
until you get one result.
你不用紧张
I wouldn't sweat it.
如果有95%的特质符合某一个派系
95% get the faction of their origin,
那就是你的归属了
and from the looks of you...
这是什么
What is it?
喝了它
Bottoms up.
选吧
Choose.
就是现在  不然就太迟了
Now. Before it's too late.
为何  我要用它们来做什么
Why? What Will I do With them?
选择
Choose.
告诉我
Just tell me.
小狗
Puppy!
快起来
Get up.
我们要赶在监督者来之前赶紧从后门出去
We're going out the back door before a supervisor comes.
-我的测试结果是什么    -快来
- But what was my result?  - Come on!
怎么了
What happened?
你得和你父母说血清让你身体不舒服
You're going to tell your family that the serum made you sick
是我让你回去的  知道了吗
and that I sent you home. All right?
不  我的测试结果呢
No, but what was my result?
无私派
Abnegation.
还有博学派 无畏派
And Erudite. And Dauntless.
怎么还有无畏派
Dauntless...
你的测试结果是不确定的
Your results were inconclusive.
那不可能  这没道理啊
That's impossible. It doesn't make any sense.
不  不是不可能的
No. Not impossible.
只是极其罕见罢了
It's just extremely rare.
他们称你这类人为"分歧者"
They call it "Divergent."
你不能和其他人谈及此事  就算是你的父母也不行
You can't tell anyone about this. Not even your parents.
对世界而言  你得到的测试结果是无私派
As far as the world is concerned, you received an Abnegation result
因为这将是我输入系统的结果
because that is what I manually entered.
那我在选择仪式上该怎么做
So what am I supposed to do at the choosing ceremony?
我本应学到我该做什么
I was supposed to learn what to do.
这个测试的目的是告诉我应该选择哪个派系
This was supposed to tell me what faction to choose, the test.
我们需要相信测试结果
We're supposed to trust the test.
测试对你无效
The test didn't work on you.
你必须相信你自己
You have to trust yourself.
你今天怎么了
What happened to you today?
测试后你去哪了
Where did you go after your test?
我不舒服  所以他们提前送我回来了
I got sick, so they sent me home early.
你完成测试了吗
Did you finish your test?
完成了
Mmm-hmm.
你的测试结果是什么
What was your result?
你的呢
What was yours?
你怎么都不和我说一声就离开了
Why did you just leave without telling anybody?
我不舒服
I was sick.
碧翠丝
Beatrice...
我想你还不明白我们现在的处境
I don't think you understand the level of scrutiny we're under.
他们竭尽所能的诋毁我们的声誉
They're doing everything they can to discredit us right now.
谁
Who is?
博学派
Erudite.
他们认为博学派才应该是执政派系  而不是我们无私派
They believe that they should be the governing faction, not us.
所以你现在要多加小心  明白吗
So you have to be careful right now, okay?
甚至连马库斯都受到了攻击
Even Marcus is under attack.
为什么
For what?
不过是一些谣言
It's an old accusation.
说他虐待他的儿子
That he mistreated his son
因此他儿子才叛变去了无畏派
and that's why the boy defected.
-真的是这样吗    -不是的
- Is that true?  - No.
当然不是
Of course not.
孩子转派有很多的理由
Children defect for all kinds of reasons.
别在这待太久了  你们需要睡个好觉
Don't take too long in here. You need a good night's sleep...
为了明天的选派仪式
For tomorrow.
我
I, um...
我们爱你们
We love you.
晚安
Good night.
亲爱的  我为你感到自豪
I'm so proud of you, honey.
-碧翠丝    -什么事
- Beatrice?  - What?
明天我们选择的时候
Tomorrow when we choose...
你一定要多替家人想想
You have to think of the family.
我知道
Yeah.
但你也要为自己着想
But you also have to think of yourself.
请各派系在自己指定区域集合
Factions, please gather in your assigned areas.
早上好  珍宁
Morning, Jeanine.
早上好  安德鲁  马库斯还好吧
Good morning, Andrew. How is Marcus holding up?
和我们预料的一样好
As well as can be expected.
我们必须找出散播流言的始作俑者
We need to find out who's behind these rumors.
我想我们都知道是谁
I think we all know who it is.
如果是我们博学派的人  我保证我会找出是谁的
If it's someone from Erudite, I promise I'll find out who.
这些是你的孩子啊
These are your children.
我还不知道他们今天选择派系呢
I don't think I knew they were choosing today.
-你叫什么    -我叫凯莱布
- What's your name?  - I'm... I'm Caleb.
很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
我是珍宁·马修斯
Jeanine Matthews.
你是
And you are?
这是碧翠丝
This is Beatrice.
你们今天都需要作出重大的决定
Well, you both have a big decision to make today.
我相信你们的父母  无论你们选择哪个派系都会支持你们的
I'm sure your parents will support whatever choice you make.
这好像也没什么可选择的
That's not supposed to be a choice.
测试结果已经决定我们该选什么
The test should tell us what to do.
你仍然拥有选择的权利
You're still free to choose.
但你并不想要我们自由选择
But you don't really want that.
碧翠丝
Beatrice...
我想要你认清自己的本质
I want you to choose who you truly are
以及自己真正的归属
and where you truly belong.
不是一时的心血来潮  也不是因为你自己的臆想
Not on a whim. Not because you wish you were someone you're not.
而是因为你真的了解自己
But because you honestly know yourself.
我想要你作出明智的选择
I want you to choose wisely.
我也知道你会这么做的
And I know you will.
派系制度就像一个生物
The faction system is a living being
而你们就是组成这个生物的细胞
composed of cells, all of you.
这个制度得以生存和繁荣的唯一方法
And the only way it can survive and thrive
就是你们每一个人都各得其所
is for each of you to claim your rightful place.
只有认清自己本质的人才会有前途
The future belongs to those who know where they belong.
当我们离开这个房间
When we leave this room,
你们将不再是彼此的家属
you will no longer be dependents
而是社会中不可缺少的一员
but full-fledged members of our society.
派系高于血缘
Faction before blood.
我爱你
I love you...
无论结果如何
No matter what.
乔纳森·齐格勒
Jonathan Ziegler.
博学派
Erudite.
杰弗里·耶茨
Jeffrey Yates.
无畏派
Dauntless.
摩根·斯托克斯
Morgan Stokes.
友好派
Amity.
克莱儿·萨特伦  诚实派
Claire Satron. Candor.
山姆·罗伯森  无私派
Sam Robertson. Abnegation.
凯莱布·普赖尔
Caleb Prior.
博学派
Erudite.
请大家保持安静
Quiet, please.
碧翠丝·普赖尔
Beatrice Prior.
无畏派
Dauntless.
欢迎来到无畏派
Welcome to Dauntless!
快点  我们走
Come on! Let's go!
快
Come on!
不好意思
Sorry.
你做到了
You made it.
-我是克里斯蒂娜    -碧翠丝
- I'm Christina.  - Beatrice.
他们是想杀了我  还是想杀了我们
Is it just me or are they trying to kill us?
准备好
Get ready!
太好了
Yeah!
-他们跳车了    -什么
- They're jumping.  - What?
如果你不跳的话会怎么样
What if you don't jump?
你觉得呢  那样你就会成为无派系的流浪者
What do you think? You'll be factionless.
祝你好运  艾尔
Good luck, Al.
哇
Whoa!
-一起吗    -好的
- Together?  - Yeah.
1  2  3
One, two, three...
好了  都听好
All right, listen up!
我是埃里克  你们的领路人之一
I'm Eric. I'm one of your leaders.
如果你们想要加入无畏派  这就是进去的路
If you want to enter Dauntless, this is the way in.
如果你们没有跳下去的勇气  那么你们就不属于无畏派
And if you don't have the guts to jump, then you don't belong in Dauntless.
那洞底下是有水还是什么吗
Is there water at the bottom or something?
你跳下去就知道了
I guess you'll find out.
或者不跳
Or not.
我们刚从车上跳下来  他们又想我们跳
We just jumped. They want us to jump again?
必定会有人第一个跳  你们有谁要当这第一人呢
Someone's gotta go first. Who's it gonna be?
我
Me.
就这样  呆子  把衣服脱了
Yeah, stiff, take it off!
你还是穿回去吧
Put it back on!
你是今天的第一个
Today, Initiate.
怎么  你被推下来了吗
What, you get pushed?
没有
No.
你叫什么
What's your name?
我叫...
It's...
是很难读的名字吗
Is that a hard one?
如果你想的话可以换个名字  但你得想个好的名字
You can pick a new one if you want, but make it good.
因为不会再有第二次换名字的机会的
You don't get to pick again.
好吧  我的名字是翠丝
Okay. My name's Tris.
第一个跳的人  翠丝
First jumper, Tris!
欢迎来到无畏派
Welcome to Dauntless.
生来就是无畏派的人跟着劳伦  其他人跟着我
Dauntless-born, go with Lauren, transfers stay with me.
来
Go.
这边来
This way.
大多数时间  我在情报机关工作
Most of the time I work in Intelligence,
但在你们训练期间  我会是你们的教练
but during your training, I'll be your instructor.
我的名字是四号
My name's Four.
4  就是数字4吗
Four, like the number?
是的  就是数字
Exactly, like the number.
怎么  1到3的数字被人用了吗
What happened, one through three were taken?
你叫什么
What's your name?
克里斯蒂娜
Christina.
那好  克里斯蒂娜
Well, Christina.
我现在给你先上第一节课
The first lesson you learn from me
如果你想在这活下去
if you wanna survive here,
就把你的嘴闭上
is keep your mouth shut.
听明白了吗
Do you understand me?
明白
Yes.
那就好
Good.
大家跟着我
Follow me.
这里是"深坑"
This is The Pit.
你们在无畏派期间生活的中心
The center of life here at Dauntless.
接下来的十周  你们将睡在这里
You're gonna be sleeping here for the next 10 weeks.
有分男女的吗
Girls or boys?
没有
Both.
-太好了 -还行吧
- Nice.  - That works.
如果你们喜欢这  那你们一定会爱上卫生间的
If you like this, you're gonna love the bathroom.
太好了
Great.
好吧
Okay...
-不是吧  -就没有其他地方了吗
- Seriously?  - Is there no other area?
你开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
你们诚实派的人该觉得在家似的
You should feel right at home, Candor.
这里所有地方都是开放式的
Everything out in the open.
这是在开玩笑吗
Is this a joke?
快换衣服
Get changed.
好吧  有谁要洗浴吗
Right. Shower, anyone?
美腿啊  呆子
Nice legs, stiff.
-嘿    -你怎么样
- Hey.  - How you doin'?
我们坐这吧
Shall we sit there?
你以前从来没看过汉堡包吗
Have you never seen a hamburger before?
不  我看过  只是从来没有吃过
No, I've seen one. I just have never eaten one.
无私派的人都是吃素食的
Abnegation eat plain food.
不放沙拉  只放少量调味品的素食
Plant-based diet with no sauces and a minimum of seasoning.
那你吃的是哪本教科书
Which textbook did you swallow?
我也很高兴见到你  我是威尔  来自博学派
Nice to meet you, too. I'm Will. Erudite.
你当然是博学派的
Of course you are.
无意冒犯  但我没想到无私派的人居然也是要吃饭的
No offense, but I'm surprised Abnegation even eats at all.
太自私了  对吧  难怪你要离开
Too selfish, right? No wonder you left.
你肯定非常自信  才敢和诚实派的人交朋友
You gotta be pretty self-confident to be friends with a Candor.
你这话是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
你们不会思虑
You have no filter.
说话都不经过大脑思考
You say the first thing that comes into your head.
比如"你是个白痴"吗
You mean like, "You're an idiot"?
说得好  至少我们说的是真话
Nice one, Al. At least we tell the truth.
博学派的人也说真话  因为我们掌握了事实
Erudite can tell the truth because we have the facts.
我不想要听到你们说你们以前的派系
I don't want to hear about your old factions.
你们现在是无畏派的人了
You're Dauntless now.
你也是个转派的吗  还是生来就是无畏派的
Were you a transfer, too? Or Dauntless-born?
你在开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
没有
No.
是什么让你觉得你有资格和我说话
What makes you think you can talk to me?
是...
It...
肯定是因为你很平易近人
Must be because you're so approachable.
你给我小心了
Careful.
四号
Four...
我的朋友  你还真是有死亡愿望
You, my friend, have a death wish.
你知道吗  他是他们那届首屈一指的人物
You know, he was first in his class.
领导们曾两次招募他进入"领导层"
They tried to recruit him for leadership twice,
但都被他拒绝了
but he said no.
新来的成员们  站起来
Initiates, stand.
你们选择进入这个战士的派系
You have chosen to join the warrior faction
我们的任务是保护这个城市及其居民
tasked with the defense of this city and all its inhabitants.
你们要将勇敢的行为当成家常便饭
We believe in ordinary acts of bravery
要有为其他人
and the courage that drives one person
挺身而出的勇气
to stand up for another.
谨记这点
Respect that.
做我们无畏派的自豪
Do us proud.
干嘛呢
Whoa!
我要在两分钟后看到你们所有人在"深坑"
I want everyone in The Pit. Two minutes.
新生训练总共有两个阶段
There are two stages of training.
第一阶段是身体训练
The first is physical.
把你的身体逼到极限  你们就能掌握战斗的方法
Push your bodies to the breaking point and you'll master the methods of combat.
第二阶段是精神训练  同样要打破极限
The second is mental. Again, breaking point.
你们将要面对你们最大的恐惧  并且征服他们  不然你们就会被恐惧征服
You'll face your worst fears and conquer them unless they get you first.
你们的训练会和来自无畏派家庭的人分开
You'll be trained separately from the Dauntless-born,
但你们的排名是一起的
but you'll be ranked together.
新生训练之后  你们的排名会决定你们进入什么工作岗位
After initiations, rankings will determine what jobs you move into.
领导层  守卫
Leadership, guarding the fence,
或者是防止流浪者自相残杀
or keeping the Factionless from killing each other.
排名也会决定谁被开除出无畏派
The rankings will also determine who gets cut.
开除?
Cut?
每个阶段训练结束后  排名最低的人就会被踢出无畏派
At the end of each stage of training, the lowest-ranking Initiates will be leaving us.
开除后去做什么
To do what?
你们不能回家  所以只能成为流浪者
There's no going home to your families, so you'd live factionless.
为什么我们之前不知道这个
Why didn't we know that?
这是新的规则
It's a new rule.
新规则  之前就该有人告诉我们这个
A new rule? Somebody should have told us that.
为什么
Why?
那样你们会作出不一样的选择吗
Would you have chosen differently?
因为恐惧吗
Out of fear?
如果是那样的话  你们最好现在就离开
I mean, if that's the case, you might as well get out now.
如果你真是我们的一员  你就不会担心你会失败
If you're really one of us, it won't matter to you that you might fail.
你们选择了我们
Now you chose us.
现在该我们对你们进行选择了
Now we get to choose you.
从统计学的角度来说  你应该至少有一次击中目标了
Statistically speaking, you should have hit the target at least once by now.
即使是意外击中的
Even by accident.
嘿  这里出什么事了
Hey. What have you got?
流浪者  什么都没做
Factionless. Not doing anything.
快看  呆子  那就是你的新家了
Check it out, stiff. That's gonna be your new family.
过去说声"你好"
Go say "Hi."
你准备好来些真正的打斗了吗
You ready for some real fighting?
还差得远呢
Not even close.
第一个跳的人
First jumper!
出来和人赛一场
In the ring.
最后一个跳的人
Last jumper!
战斗时间到了
Time to fight.
我们需要打多久
How long do we fight for?
直到有人打不动为止
Till one of you can't continue.
或者其中之一投降
Or one of you concedes.
那是旧规矩
According to the old rules.
新规矩是  不能有人投降
New rules, no one concedes.
你真的想要在她们第一次战斗中就失去一个吗
You really want to lose 'em on their first fight?
一个勇敢的人是永远不会投降的
A brave man never surrenders.
你该庆幸我们战斗的时候没有这规矩
Lucky for you, those weren't the rules when we fought.
这场战斗会给你们记分  倾尽全力吧
You'll be scored on this, so fight hard.
开始
Go!
不要怕  呆子
Don't be scared, stiff!
很好  翠丝
Nice, Tris!
-打的好    -就这样
- Nice.  - Yeah!
好了  大家都到这来
All right, guys, over here.
听好了
Listen up.
知道这块板是干什么的吗
Know what this board is?
这就是你们的生活
It's your life.
我们每天都会给你们排名
We grade you every day.
如果第一阶段的训练结束时  你们还在板的红色部分
If you're still in the red by the end of the first stage,
那你们就出局了
you're out.
我永远也不会成功的
I'm never gonna make it.
不  你会成功的
Yes, you are.
我是这最弱的一个
I'm the weakest one here.
那你能成为进步最快的
Then you'll be most improved.
你是诚实派的人  你不该撒谎的
You're Candor. You're not supposed to lie.
我以前确实是诚实派的  而且我现在也没说谎
I was Candor. And I'm not lying.
如果他们开除我  我觉得我父母会带我回去的
If they cut me, I think my parents would take me back.
不  制度不是这么运行的
No, it doesn't work like that.
即便他们想要接你回去  他们的派系也不会允许的
Even if they wanted to, their faction wouldn't allow it.
即便我父母会带我回去
Even if my parents would take me back,
我也不再属于无私派了
I wouldn't belong there anymore.
气氛变得压抑了
This is getting depressing.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道我们该干嘛吗  我们应该去刺个刺青
You know what we should do? Get tattoos.
你知道他们有一个你脸的刺青吗?
Did you know they had a tattoo of your face?
-喜欢吗?     -当然
- Like it?  - Yeah.
-你想刺在哪里?     -我不知道
- Where would you get it?  - I don't know.
你觉得我该刺在哪?
Where do you suggest?
只要你想  哪里都可以
Anywhere you want.
这儿  刺这还不错
Here, it's this thing here.
你还记得我  对吧?
You remember me, right?
我只是在想如果你能...
I was just wondering if you could...
不行
No.
我只负责刺青
I just do tattoos.
好吧
Okay.
我想要刺这个
I'd like this one.
拜托了
Please.
我能不能问一下...
Can I just ask you...
你不该选择无畏派的
You made a mistake choosing Dauntless.
-他们会发现你...    -谁?
- They'll find out about you...  - Who?
谁会?
Who Will?
你对其构成威胁的人们
The people you're a threat to.
什么人们?   谁  无畏派吗?
What people? Who, Dauntless?
不  整个社会
No, society.
如果你不能融入一个派系  他们就无法控制你
If you don't fit into a category, they can't control you.
我不明白
I don't get it.
我是无畏派的人  我也将变得无所畏惧
I'm Dauntless. I'm going to be Dauntless.
所以我选择无畏派
I chose Dauntless.
为你着想  我希望如此
For your sake, I hope so.
你太弱了  你连肌肉都没有
You're weak. You have no muscle.
像你这样下去  你永远不会赢的
You're never gonna win, not like that.
多谢指教
That's good to know.
对  你需要使用你整个身体
Yeah, you have to use your whole body.
从这里发力
Keep tension here.
-好的...    -开始进攻
- Okay...  - And go on offense.
你速度很快  如果你先进攻就可以赢
You're fast, so you could win if you attack first.
你进去  猛刺喉咙
You get inside, you jab to the throat.
四号!
Four!
继续
Keep working.
对不起  威尔
Sorry about that, Will.
加油  克里斯
Come on, Chris.
停...停!
Stop... Stop!
我不打了  我不打了
I'm done. I'm done.
你想要停下来吗?
You need to stop?
那好
Okay.
让我来帮你一把
Let me give you a hand.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了  大家都休息下吧
All right, let's everyone take a break!
你感觉好些了吗?
You feelin' a little better?
是  我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
哇!
Whoa!
抓住铁轨
Grab the rail.
或者掉下去
Or don't.
我给你三个选择
You've got three options.
抓住铁轨  我会忘记你的怯懦
Hang there and I'll forget your cowardice.
掉下去摔死
Fall and die.
或者放弃
Or give up.
但是如果你放弃了  你就要被踢出无畏派了
But if you give up, you're out.
加油  克里斯
Come on, Chris!
时间到
Time!
无畏派从不放弃
Dauntless never give up.
作为无畏派  我们为保护
As Dauntless, we fight to protect
围栏内的每个生命而奋斗  决不允许失败
every life inside the fence, without fail.
这就是我们用这种方式训练你的原因
That's why we train you the way we do.
教会你不要放弃
To teach you not to give up.
并找出具备这些素质的合适人选
And to find out who has what it takes.
尽管城市已经太平好多年了
Even though it's been quiet out there for years,
但情况随时都可能发生变化
that could change at any moment.
因此我们必须时刻准备好一切
So we have to be ready for everything.
喔!
Whoo!
-什么在那里?     -怪物
- What's out there?  - Monsters.
友好派的农场
Amity farms.
这个我知道  但我是指农场之外?
No, I know. But beyond that?
那些战争留下来的废墟
Places that never recovered from the war.
你知道吗?
Do you know?
防护墙的建立是有它的理由的
Let's just say they built their fence for a reason.
天呐!
Man!
你还挺擅长这个的
You're kinda good at this.
快
Come on.
这一投太可悲了
That was pathetic.
它滑下去了
It slipped.
那就把它捡回来
Well, go get it!
什么  在他们投的时候捡吗?
What, while they're throwing?
你怕了吗?
Are you afraid?
怕被空中的飞刀刺伤吗?   当然了
Of getting stabbed by an airborne knife? Yeah.
所有人都停下
Everybody stop.
你站在靶子的前面去
Stand in front of the target.
四号  帮我一下
Four, gimme a hand here.
当他扔那些飞刀的时候你就站在那儿
You're gonna stand there while he throws those knives.
如果我看到你畏缩  你就给我卷铺盖走人
And if I see you flinch, you're out.
你在这必须学到一点  那就是命令是不容选择的
One thing you will learn here is that orders are not optional.
停下来
Stop.
任何人都可以站在靶子前面  这不能证明什么
Anyone can stand in front of a target. It doesn't prove anything.
那么让你来接替他的位置应该是件很轻松的事喽
Then it should be easy for you to take his place.
规则不变
Same rules apply.
拜托  四号
Oh, come on, Four.
再投近一点
You can get closer than that.
你要我给她一点点微调吗?
You want me to give her a little trim?
是的  也许稍稍往下移点
Yeah, maybe just a little off the top.
给你的勇气加点分  孩子
Points for bravery, stiff.
但是也抵不过你因顶撞而丢掉的分
Not as many as you just lost for opening your mouth.
以后给我注意点
Now watch yourself.
我们是训练士兵  而不是叛徒
We train soldiers, not rebels.
我们今天的训练就到这里  都给我出去
But we're done for today. Get out.
-你没事吧?     -你割到我了
-You all right? -You cut me.
我故意的
I meant to.
你在逗我吗
You meant to?
你认为他会让你毫发无伤的离开吗
You think he was gonna let you off without a scratch?
如果我没有击中你  你还要站在那里
You'd still be standing there if I hadn't hit you.
所以  我应该感谢你  对吗
So am I supposed to thank you?
你应该更识时务点
You're supposed to be smart.
如果我想伤害你  我早已经动手了
If I wanted to hurt you, I would have.
她来了
There she is.
你是不是不想活了
You do have a death wish.
我不敢相信你对埃里克说了那番话
I can't believe you said that to Eric.
你是唯一一个反对他的人
You're the only one who's ever stood up to him.
看看你的耳朵  让我们来清理一下
Look at your ear. Let's get you cleaned up.
嘿  翠丝
Hey, Tris.
你酷毙了
That was cool.
谢谢了
Thanks.
令人刮目相看嘛  呆子  恭喜你
Impressive, stiff. Congrats.
闭嘴
Shut up.
怎么了  你现在可出名了
What? Hey, you're famous now.
我的意思是  不是因为与埃里克有关
I mean, not because of the thing with Eric.
而是因为你上新闻了  你听
You're in the news. Yeah, listen.
近日离开的安德鲁·普赖尔的一对儿女
"The recent transfers of Beatrice and Caleb Prior,
碧翠丝·普赖尔和凯莱布·普赖尔
"children of Andrew Prior,
引发了人们对无私派
"call into question the soundness
教育方法和价值观的质疑
"of Abnegation's teachings and values.
是什么促使他们离开?
"What prompted them to leave?
也许答案就在于整个派系堕落的思想
"Perhaps the answer lies in the corrupted ideal of an entire faction.
剽窃资源  领袖无能
"The theft of resources, the general incompetence,
虐待自己的子女
"the abuse of their children."
他们像对待马库斯·伊顿的孩子一样打你了吗?
Did they beat you, like Marcus Eaton's kid?
他们没有打任何人  他们是好人
They didn't beat anyone. They're good people.
对  那是你离开的原因?
Right. And that's why you left?
我说错什么话了吗?
Was it something I said?
-他是个傻瓜    -是的
- He's an idiot.  - Yeah.
是啊  没关系
Yeah. That's okay.
她来无畏派做什么?
What's she doing at Dauntless?
普赖尔
Prior.
你是安德鲁·普赖尔的女儿  对吧?
You're Andrew Prior's daughter, aren't you?
碧翠丝
Beatrice.
现在叫翠丝了
It's just Tris now.
翠丝这个名字我喜欢
Tris, I like that.
嗯
Hmm.
你做了个很棒的决定  翠丝  尽管让你的父母失望了
You made an impressive choice, Tris, despite your parents.
也没有遵循你的测试结果
And your test result.
你看过我的测试结果了?
You've seen my test result?
当然
Of course.
我很高兴你足够聪明  可以知道自己内心的想法
I'm glad you were smart enough to know your own mind.
如果你需要什么  尽管开口
Let me know if you ever need anything.
这真是太奇怪了
Well, that was weird.
我也这么觉得
Yeah.
你觉得是怎么回事?
What do you think is goin' on?
我敢打赌  他们正在追捕分歧者
I bet they're hunting Divergents.
他们这几天都在讨论这事
That's all they talk about at Erudite these days.
等等  分歧者真的存在吗?
Wait. Divergents are real?
快点  艾尔
Come on, Al.
第一场战斗  彼得对阵翠丝
First fight. Peter versus Tris.
什么?
What?
嗯  哦
Uh-Oh.
又是埃里克
It's Eric.
他只是想报复你
He's just trying to get back at you.
-嘿    -怎么了
-Hey. -What?
还记得我给你说过的  关于进攻的话吗
Remember what I said about attack?
先发制人  直击喉咙
First shot, right to the throat.
盯紧他
And you watch him.
他攻击时脚会先动
He steps before he punches.
记住了吗
All right?
记住了
Mmm.
好了  呆子  你准备好了吗
All right there, stiff?
别哭出来哟
Look like you're about to cry.
哭出来的话也许会好受点
Might take it easy on you if you cry.
加油  翠丝
Come on, Tris.
站起来  站起来
Get up. Get up.
来嘛  别像小孩子那样打架
Come on. Stop playin' with each other.
哇  你看起来...
Wow. You look...
看起来很糟糕
Look bad.
我躺在这多久了?
How long have I been here?
差不多一天了
About a day.
都一天了?
A day?
你看到记分牌了吗?   我排在第几?
Have you seen the scoreboard? Where am I?
你在合格线下面
You got below the line.
你为什么要穿着这些背心?
Why are you wearing those vests?
我们要进行模拟战争
War games.
哇  你在做什么
Whoa. What are you doing?
-我也要去    -不行
- I'm coming.  - You can't.
埃里克说你可以卷铺盖走人了
Eric says you're done.
什么?
What?
他说你出局了
He said you're out.
你父亲在议会  翠丝
Your father's on the council, Tris.
也许他们会开个先例让你回家
Maybe they'll make an exception and let you go home.
我们很抱歉  翠丝
We're sorry, Tris.
我们要走了  不然该错过火车了
We gotta go. We're gonna miss the train.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
-再见    -再见
-Bye. -Bye.
谢谢
Thanks.
你好
Hi.
-你好    -你来这儿做什么?
- Hi.  - What are you doing here?
我刚想通了  我得坚持下去
I just figured that I had to make it.
谁让你出来了?
Who let you out?
我自己
I did.
你自己?
You did?
好吧
Okay.
你先坐下吧
Let's sit you down.
这个游戏很简单  等同于争夺旗帜
The game's simple. It's like Capture the Flag.
选好你们的武器
Weapon of choice.
你叫这作"枪"吗
You call that a gun?
这是刺激神经的飞镖
Neuro-stim dart.
能够模拟真实枪伤的痛苦
Simulates the pain of a real gunshot wound.
仅仅持续几分钟
Only lasts a couple minutes.
分两队  四号和我是队长
Two teams. Four and I are captains.
你先挑队员吧
You pick first.
那好  爱德华
Okay. Edward.
我选翠丝
I'll take the stiff.
噢  故意挑弱的一个
Oh. Picking the weak ones
等你输了后就可以找个替罪羊了
so you've got someone to blame when you lose.
差不多吧
Something like that.
埃里克的队去哪儿了?
Where did Eric's team go?
他们一定到那边去了
They must have gone to the end.
好的  关灯
All right. Lights off.
都过来  快
Gather around. Come on.
好了  你们打算怎么样?
Okay. What's your strategy?
我们把旗子藏的足够好  这样他们就找不到了
We can hide the flag well enough so they can't find it.
我们派一个小组去侦察他们的位置  看能否找到他们的旗子
Let's send out a team to scout their location. See if we can find their flag.
我们可以用闪电战  纯武力打败他们
I say we blitz them. Just beat them with sheer force.
是的  那是快速输掉比赛最好的方法
Yeah, that's the best way to lose quickly.
快速结束比赛  他们不会想到的
End this quickly, they won't expect it.
我们不知道他们在哪儿
We don't know where they are.
好吧  我们分成两组  防守组和进攻组
Okay, we split into two groups, defense and offense.
谁让你说了算的?
Who put you in charge?
总要有人做个决定
Someone has to make a decision.
我们需要更具进攻性
We need to be more aggressive.
我们得更聪明些
We need to be smart about it.
你不会是想跳下来吧
You're not gonna jump, are you?
不  我只是想找到一个好的制高点
No, I'm just trying to get a good vantage point.
这主意不错
Good thinking.
你没必要和我一起来
You don't have to come with me.
放松点 你太紧张了
You should go easy. You took a beating.
没想到你连这都注意到了
I'm surprised you noticed.
我看到你在战斗期间离开了
I saw you leave during the fight.
嗯  好吧  我不想看到他们在那吵架
Yeah, well, it's not something I wanted to watch.
嘿!
Hey!
你还好吗?
You good?
你呢?
You Okay?
是的  我很好
Yeah. I'm fine.
这里够高了
This is high enough.
不  我们还得往上
No, we need to go higher.
你还好吗?
You all right?
你恐高吧
You're afraid of heights.
每个人都有害怕的东西
Everyone's afraid of something.
我还以为你什么都不怕呢
I didn't think you were afraid of anything.
加油  翠丝
Come on, Tris.
还不够高吗?
Really?
你还是人类吗?
Are you even human?
没那么糟糕嘛
This isn't so bad.
视野真好
Good eye.
看!
Look!
在那儿
There it is.
好的  你打算怎么做
All right. What's your plan?
我们分成两组
We split into two groups.
我们从这边上去  你们其余人拖住埃里克
We'll go up this side and let the rest of you engage Eric.
-我看到他们了    -赶紧走
- I can see 'em.  - Go! Go!
给我点亮光
Light 'em up!
还有两个  我再靠近些
There's two more! I'm gonna move in closer!
跟着我  走!
Follow me. Go!
-看紧你的右侧!     -快快快
- Watch on your right!  - Go, go, go.
-走    -克里斯蒂娜  我们走!
- Go.  - Christina, let's go!
拖住他们  拖住他们
Get 'em, get 'em!
这边!
This way!
-好的    -掩护我!
- All right.  - Cover me!
疼的话哼一声
Tell me if this hurts.
你哼给我听吧
You tell me.
你个婊子
You bitch!
混蛋
Asshole.
太酷了!
That was awesome!
我需要掩护!
Get covered!
去吧  翠丝!  我来掩护你
Go, Tris! I'll guard.
喔!
Whoo!
游戏结束!
Game over!
干得好  翠丝!
Good job, Tris!
嘿  翠丝!
Hey, Tris!
-怎么了?     -跟我们来
- Yeah?  - Come with us.
去哪儿?
Where you going?
搭顺风车回去
Shortcut back.
算是新生的一个仪式吧  无畏派的传统了
A little initiation ritual, Dauntless style.
哇
Wow.
好的  我们走
All right, let's do this!
-好的  你还好吗?     -我很好
- All right, you good?  - Good.
-好  出发  出发!     -抓紧了
- Yeah. Go, go!  - Hang tight.
-飞吧  亲爱的    -哇
- Fly, baby.  - Whoo!
轮到你了
You're up.
好的  来吧
All right, do it!
加油  姑娘们
Come on, girl.
去吧  翠丝
Go for it! Do it, Tris!
像小鸟一样飞翔
Like flying!
不要忘了到底部时拉手闸
Don't forget to pull the brake at the bottom!
好的
Okay.
出发
Go.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
带子很好
Harness is good.
-拉手闸!     -拉手闸!
-Pull the brake! -Pull the brake!
太棒了
Yeah!
翠丝!
Tris!
-嗨    -嗨
-Hey -Hey
祝贺你
Congratulations.
谢谢
Thanks.
我只是想说  你今天晚上发挥的很好
You know, I wanted to say that you were really good tonight.
你很勇敢
You were brave.
是的
Yeah.
不过  你应该回到你的朋友那里
Anyway, you should get back to your friends.
好的
Okay.
如果你排到了红线以上
If you're ranked above the red line,
你就会到达训练的第二阶段
you'll move on to the second stage of training.
如果你低于红线  我们就不会在你身上再浪费时间
If you're below it, we'll waste no more time on you.
这是你的排名
Here are your rankings.
太棒了
Nice.
你做到了
You made it.
你成功了  翠丝
You made it, Tris.
-知道了    -谢谢
-Got it. -Thank you.
给你
Here you go.
我们已经通过了第一阶段的训练  这都是我们的奖励
So we pass the first stage of training, and this is our reward.
扔上来
Toss it up!
太棒了
Glamorous.
妈妈?
Mom?
噢  我的宝贝姑娘!
Oh, my girl!
妈妈  你在这儿做什么?
Mom, what are you doing here?
我知道他们迟早会派你来这儿
I knew they'd assign you here sooner or later.
看看你!   天呐  你既强健又漂亮
Look at you! God, you're so strong and beautiful.
妈妈  你不能呆在这儿
Mom, you can't be here.
我知道  可是你在这里太危险了
I know, but you're in danger.
什么?
What?
我问你一些事情
I had to ask you something.
你参加能力倾向测试那天并没有生病  对不?
You weren't sick the day you took your aptitude test, were you?
-怎么了?     -你测试的结果是什么?
-Why? -What were your test results?
亲爱的  没事的  你可以告诉我
Honey, it's okay. You can tell me.
他们...  他们不确定
They were... They were inconclusive.
是分歧者吗?
Divergent?
你不能告诉任何人  就算是朋友  导师也不能告诉他们
You can't tell anyone. You can't tell your friends,
你不能相信任何人
your instructors. You can't trust anyone.
我不会的
I'm not.
人们都恐惧分歧者
People have always been so threatened by Divergents.
现在博学派正在到处搜寻分歧者
But now Erudite is looking for them everywhere.
他们的巡查越来越密集了
They're actively seeking them out.
为什么要这么做
Why?
妈妈  我到底是什么?
Mom, what am I?
你和周围环境不相容  因为你的思维太广泛
You don't conform. Your mind works in a million different ways.
他们害怕你
They're scared of you.
训练的第二阶段是你最危险的时候
Stage two of training is where you are most at risk.
他们会进入你的思想看你如何面对恐惧
They're gonna get inside your head and watch how you respond to fear.
如果你能坚持下去  你是可以通过测试的
But you can pass. You can make it through Dauntless.
我以前见到过了
I have seen it before.
你怎么这么了解无畏派?
How do you know so much about this? About Dauntless?
不要管我了  不要让他们知道你是谁
Never mind about me. Do not let them know who you are.
等等!   等等!   你是无畏派的吗?
Wait! Wait! Were you Dauntless?
-听着    -嘿
-Listen. -Hey!
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
卡车装满了  我们该走了
Truck's loaded. Let's go.
他们对她做了什么?
What did they do to her?
到你了  翠丝
Tris.
坐下
Take a seat.
我将给你注射一种刺激大脑中
I'm going to inject you with a serum that stimulates
处理恐惧部分的血清
the part of your brain that processes fear.
好极了
Great.
它会产生幻觉
It incluces a hallucination,
然后血清里的发送器
and then transmitters in the serum
能让我看到你脑中的影像
allow me to see the images in your mind.
你可以看到我的思想?
You can see inside my mind?
没错
Mmm-hmm.
躺下
Lay back.
现在  你要面对来自你心底深处的恐惧  翠丝
Now, you're gonna be facing your worst fears, Tris.
大多数人有十到十五个令他们非常恐惧的事物
Most people have 10 to 15 really bad ones.
你必须冷静下来
You have to calm yourself.
减缓你的心跳和呼吸频率
Slow your heart rate and your breathing,
处理好你眼前的事情
and deal with what's in front of you.
勇敢些
Be brave.
那些不是真实的
This isn't real.
好了  好了
It's all right, it's all right.
你还好吗?
You okay?
翠丝  你觉得你在幻觉里呆了多久
How long do you think you were in the hallucination, Tris?
-大概20分钟?     -只有3分钟
- Twenty minutes?  - Three.
比平均水平快了四倍
Four times faster than the average.
我还从没有见过有谁能第一次就做得这么好
I've never seen anyone do that well the first time.
你怎么摆脱那些鸟的?
How did you get rid of the birds?
传送过来的画像不清晰
The image wasn't clear.
额...
Um...
我只是进了水里
I just went into the water.
好的  下次就会容易很多了
Well, next time it'll be a lot easier.
我必须再做那个吗?
I have to do that again?
是的  你必须在最终考核之前多练习几次
Yeah, you have to practice several times before the final,
但你天生就是个无畏派
but you're a natural.
你没有什么好担心的
You got nothing to worry about.
我的整个身体都被这种小昆虫覆盖
My whole body was covered in these little insects.
它们在我的耳朵里  在我的喉咙里...
They were in my ears, and my throat...
我不能呼吸了
I couldn't breathe.
是的  我听说过这个人  大概两年前的样子...
Yeah, I heard about this guy, like two years ago...
他如此慌张以至于在椅子上心脏病发作了
So panicked he had a heart attack in his chair
-他几乎死过去了吗?     -什么?
-and he almost died. -What?
是的  所以我们得到了可以期盼的东西  不是吗?
Yeah, so we've got that to look forward to, right?
你好像完全没有问题
You didn't seem to have any problem at all.
我的吗? 不不不  我的天  太糟糕了
Me? No, no, my God, it was awful.
你别害怕  根本没人能超越你
Oh, come on. No one even came close to your time.
-你的表现实在很出人意表    -没错  她的出人意表
- You were amazing.  - Yeah, what's amazing is that
已经能让你驱逐出无畏派了
she's gonna knock you right out of Dauntless.
她不会这么做的
She's not gonna knock me out of Dauntless.
你看  她从排名榜上最后几位爬到最上层的位置
Look, she's gone from being the worst to one of the best.
这当中得有人当她的垫脚石
Somebody's gotta take her place at the bottom.
那个人会是谁呢  不就是你么
Who's it gonna be? You.
你可以少说几句话吗
Do you ever stop talking?
我只是想知道她是怎么做到的
I just want to know how she does it.
你到底耍了些什么小把戏
What's your trick?
我没耍过任何把戏
I don't have a trick.
从来没有人这么快就能完成那项测试
Nobody gets through it that fast.
为什么你不告诉我们你是怎么做到的
Why don't you tell us how you do it?
至少能跟你朋友们说说
At least tell your friends.
他在说什么
What's he talkin' about?
难道真有什么办法能快速通关吗
Is there some way to make it easier?
没有
No.
没有  我...我什么都没做
No, I... I'm not doing anything.
嘿!   嘿!
Hey! Hey!
这不是真的
This isn't real.
你是怎么做到的
How'd you do that?
你在说什么
What?
你是怎么把玻璃敲碎的
How'd you break the glass?
我不知道  就那样敲碎了呗
I don't know. Just did it.
真的吗
You just did it?
你的测试结果是什么
What were your test results?
你的能力倾向测试
Your aptitude test.
无私派
Abnegation.
肯定不是
I don't think so.
什么
What?
我觉得你在向我撒谎
I think you're lying to me.
为什么我要向你撒谎
Why would I lie to you?
我再问你一遍
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
你的测试结果是什么
What were your test results?
无私派
Abnegation.
你该走了
Time for you to go.
翠丝
Tris?
我只是想让你知道
Just so you know,
无畏派的人是不会那样把玻璃敲碎的
Dauntless don't break the glass like that.
我的哥哥也和你一样
My brother was like you.
到第二阶段的时候他做得非常好
During the second stage, he got good really fast.
到了最后一天的模拟考验
Last day of the simulations,
其中一个无畏派的人来到这监视他
one of the Dauntless leaders came to watch him.
然后第二天早晨  他的尸体便被发现在...
Then the next morning, we found his body
那条鸿沟里面
at the bottom of the chasm.
他们把他给杀了
They got rid of him.
是谁干的
Who did?
无畏派的领袖
Dauntless leadership.
你千万不能让他们知道你的秘密
You can't let them find out about you.
万一他们知道了会怎么样
And what if they already know?
那么你离死期不远了
Then you're already dead.
碧翠丝
Beatrice.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我有麻烦了
I'm in trouble.
怎么了
What happened?
我觉得我不适合待在无畏派
I'm not gonna make it at Dauntless.
我在那里格格不入
I don't fit in there.
你必须得适应
You have to fit in there.
我做不到
I can't.
我就是...不太喜欢他们
I'm just... I'm not like them.
他们...呵呵  只是疯了点
I mean, who is? They're crazy.
也许我可以回到无私派
Maybe I can go back to Abnegation.
-你不能这么回去    -我知道  但是...
- You can't go back.  - I know, but...
他们是绝对不会让你这么做的
They're never gonna let you do that.
-你说的是谁    -博学派那帮人
- Who?  - Erudite.
他们是不会让无私派破坏任何规则
They're not gonna let Abnegation break any more rules.
他们真的觉得自己在掌管政权么
They actually think that they're running the government now?
也许他们很快就是了
They might be soon.
等等  真的吗
Wait. Really?
博学派本就应是执政派  而不该是无私派
Erudite should be in charge. Certainly not Abnegation.
等等  凯莱布  你怎么能这样说话
Wait, hold on, Caleb. How can you say that?
这是其他帮派所希望的  而不是说无私派失败了
It's what all the other factions want, now that Abnegation failed.
不是这样的  你所说的这一切都是
No. That's just what they're telling you here...
-真的    -假的
-it's true. -It's not true.
这是假的
It's not.
他们都是骗子
There are liars here.
这些人知道怎么控制你
There are people who know how to manipulate you.
这你得知道的
You need to understand that.
碧翠丝
Beatrice.
我想你该走了
I think you should go.
派系高于血缘  对吗
Faction before blood. Yeah?
这下我明白了
Got it.
请你跟我走一趟
I need you to come with me.
快停下
Stop!
你没事吧
Are you all right?
嗯  我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
请坐下来吧
Please, sit down.
谢谢]
Thank you.
我很高兴你今天来到了这里
I'm glad you came here today.
真的吗
You are?
和新派系呆在一起开心吗
Are you happy with your new faction?
开心
Yeah.
可为什么你来这里见你的哥哥
But you came to see your brother.
我只是...我只是想跟他聊几句
I just... I just wanted to talk to him.
你见过你的父母了吗
Have you seen your parents?
还没
No.
我知道他们难以接受你的离开
It's hard to let go.
但派系高于血缘
Faction before blood.
其固然重要  但有时候确实很难实现
It's an important ideal, but sometimes difficult to fulfill.
它违背了我们最基本的人性
It goes against our fundamental human nature.
但这正是我们需要克服的弱点
But that's exactly the weakness we need to overcome.
你觉得人性是我们的弱点吗
You think that human nature is a weakness?
我认为人性是我们的敌人
I think human nature is the enemy.
是人性让我们保守秘密  撒谎  偷窃
It's human nature to keep secrets, lie, steal.
而我想根除它
And I wanna eradicate that.
我们就是想这样维持社会的和平
That's how we'll maintain a stable, peaceful society.
你会帮我的  不是吗
You would help me with that, wouldn't you?
我怎么帮你
How would I help you?
你是不是察觉到无畏派想破坏派系系统  破坏法规
You're aware that Abnegation is undermining the faction system and breaking laws,
而且还窝藏分歧者
harboring Divergents?
我不知道
I didn't know that.
如果那是真的  我会乐意离开那
But if that's true, then I'm glad that I left.
所以我得确定我是否可以
See, I need to know that I can count on you
靠你来执法
to enforce the law,
即使是那些和你亲近的人
even if it's been broken by someone close to you.
你所关爱的人也得受法规的惩处
Someone you care about.
没问题
Of course.
很好
Good.
我现在先安排车送你回去
Then I'll have my car take you back to Dauntless.
快点把她扔下去
Come on! Get her over!
快点  不然来不及了
Come on, do it! Do it!
喂
Hey!
你没事吧
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
来  我们走
Come on. Let's go.
给  穿上吧
Here, put this on.
谢谢
Thank you.
你在这里会很安全的
You'll be safe here.
对不起
Sorry.
没事
It's okay.
我真不敢相信艾尔居然会...
I can't believe Al...
你一直在向上爬  而他则不断往下滑
You're moving up through the ranks, and he's failing.
这使得他自卑
It makes him hate himself and it makes him hate you.
他只是担心受怕而已
He's just afraid.
大家都是这样
Everyone's afraid.
我知道  但恐惧的确会改变像艾尔那样的人
I know, but fear does something strange to people like Al.
但肯定不会改变你
But not you.
恐惧不会吓倒你  而是唤醒你
Fear doesn't shut you down, it wakes you up.
我已经看到了
I've seen it.
你应该躺下来了
You should lie down.
-早点睡吧    -好
- Get some sleep.  - Yeah.
我睡地板吧
I'll take the floor.
觉得怎么样
How you feeling?
好多了
Better.
不错
Good.
你昨天到哪里了
Where'd you go yesterday?
我去见我哥哥一面
To see my brother.
是不是这里对你来说有点无聊
It's getting a little boring for you here, is it?
我哥哥他说...
My brother said that...
他觉得博学派正打算推翻无私派的政府
He thinks Erudite is planning to overthrow Abnegation.
你觉得他们会这么做么
Do you think they could do that?
嗯  我觉得这的确有可能
Yeah, I do. I think it's possible.
这得看他们打算在这条路走多远
Depends how far they're willing to go.
我很担心我的父母
I'm worried about my parents.
没错
Yeah.
但我觉得你还有其他事情要去操心
But I think you got other things you need to worry about.
不是吗
Don't you?
是的
Yeah.
我得走了
I should go.
嗨
Hi.
你好
Hey.
这是你的毛衣吗
Is that your sweater?
这不是我的
No.
你昨天晚上怎么了
So what happened to you last night?
翠丝  我能和你谈几句吗
Tris, can I talk to you for a second?
听着  我只是想跟你说声对不起
Listen, I just wanted to say that I'm sorry.
我也不知道我怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with me.
你能原谅我吗  拜托了
Please, can you ever forgive me?
如果你再走过来一步  我会把你碎尸万段
If you ever come close to me again, I will kill you.
翠丝
Tris...
你给我滚开
You need to stay away from me!
你这个胆小鬼
You are a coward.
我只是不敢相信他会这么做
I just can't believe he would do that.
这根本不像他
It's not like him at all.
那是什么
What's that?
快过来吧
Come on.
噢  我的天
Oh, my God!
他大概是刚刚跳下去的
Guess he just jumped.
翠丝
Tris.
翠丝!
Tris!
让我一个人静一会儿
Leave me alone.
我很抱歉艾尔死了
I'm sorry about Al.
他是因为我而死的
It's my fault that he's dead.
不  这不是你的错  他只是作出了自己的抉择
No, it's not because of you. He made his own choice.
他是不会融合到帮派的
He would have been factionless.
他是不会通过测试的
He was not gonna pass that final test.
那么我也不会通过
Neither am I.
为什么你这么说
Why do you say that?
你知道原因的
You know why.
如果其他人知道我是分歧者  他们会把我杀了的
And as soon as all the others find out, they're gonna kill me.
我绝对不会容许这发生
I'm not gonna let that happen.
把门关上
Shut the door.
你要多加练习
You're gonna practice.
-在我的视觉里面练习吗    -不是
- In my fear landscape?  - No.
在我的视觉里练习
In mine.
我们一起来
We go in together.
你之前这么做过吗
Have you ever done this before?
没有
No, I haven't.
你真的想这么做吗
You sure you want to?
为什么这么问
Why wouldn't I?
我不知道
I don't know.
你还没有跟我说过任何关于你的事
You haven't told me anything about yourself
怎么这么快就允许我进入到你的思想里面
and now you're just gonna let me inside of your head?
你怕了?
Are you afraid of that?
你不怕?
You're not?
也不全是
No.
你恐高吗
Fear of heights.
这不是什么大事
I'm not surprised.
这不是真的
It's not real.
-我们可以跳下去    -不要这样
- We could just jump. -No.
分歧者可以跳下去
Divergent would jump.
但无畏派会跑到那栋楼去
Dauntless would get to that building.
如果你想通过那项测试  如果你不想别人发现的话
If you want to pass, if you want to avoid discovery,
你得像无畏派的人一样那么做
you have to do everything the way a Dauntless would do it.
你得去找点工具  并且以某种方式生存下去
You have to find some tool, some method to survive.
密闭空间恐惧症
Fear of confinement.
你得想办法阻止它
You have to find a way of stopping it.
想想无畏派的人会怎么做
What would a Dauntless do?
做得不错
Good!
慢慢来
Take your time.
沉住气
I'm just enjoying myself in this shrinking box.
作为无畏派的战士  你得服从命令
As a Dauntless soldier, you have to follow orders
即使你认为那不是正确的
you don't always agree with.
她是谁
Who is she?
她只是一个无辜的人
She's an innocent.
我要把她杀了
I have to kill her.
但我永远无法做到这一点
But I can never do it.
除非我把我的视线移开
Unless I look away.
为什么我们到了无私派的地方
Why are we in Abnegation?
你最后的恐惧也是你最大的恐惧
Your last fear is your worst fear.
它总是躲藏在你脑海深处
It lives in the deepest part of your mind.
麦克斯有一个儿子
Marcus had a son.
他的名字叫什么
What was his name?
托比亚斯
Tobias.
托比亚斯...
Tobias...
我只是想帮你变得更强
I'm just trying to help you to be better.
别!
No!
四号
Four?
代表四种恐惧?
Four fears?
以前四种  现在四种
Four then, four now.
我一直在尝试克服他们  但我觉得你比我更优秀
I keep going in there, but I don't think you ever lose them.
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you something?
当然可以
Sure.
你的刺青长什么样
What's your tattoo?
你想看吗
You wanna see it?
这太美了
It's amazing.
这些都是派系的图腾
The factions.
为什么你要把他们都刺上去
Why do you have all of them?
我不想只成为一个派系的成员
I don't want to be just one thing.
我不想那么做
I can't be.
我需要变得勇敢  变得无私
I want to be brave and I want to be selfless...
聪明  诚实  同时也友好
Intelligent and honest and kind.
尽管现在我还在为变得"友好"而努力
Although I'm still working on "kind."
我不想进展得这么快
I don't wanna go too fast.
没事的
It's okay.
我已经在你的心里占了一部分位置
I've already got my spot on the floor.
早安
Morning.
嘿
Hey.
来吧  我要给你看点东西
Come on. I'm gonna show you something.
好吧
Okay.
你看
Look.
-这不是博学派的人吗    -没错
- Erudite.  - Yeah.
他们每天早晨都会到这里
They're here every morning.
我已经观察他们一周了
I've been watching them for weeks.
他们在这里干什么
What are they doing at Dauntless?
在储备物资  例如电脑
Loading in supplies. Computers.
还有这个
And these.
这是什么
What is it?
我认为这是某种认知传感器
I think it's some kind of cognitive transmitter.
这东西会像血清一样注射到你的身体
You inject it like a serum.
为什么要这么做?
Why?
它可以让你更容易感受到暗示
It's supposed to make you more susceptible to suggestion,
但如果越多人被注射  那么他们就有足以组建军队的能力
but as many as they have, they could create an army.
请注意
Attention,
请所有新人到最终测试点集合
all initiates report for final testing.
All initiates report for final testing.
你已经准备好了的
You're ready.
你一定可以完成的
You can do this.
他们可以在屏幕上看到你的幻觉
They can see your hallucinations on the screen.
所以你要用无畏派的方式来通过他们的测试
So you get past your fears the way a Dauntless would,
但不要浪费时间
but do it quickly.
了解  如果我太优秀  他们会把我杀了
Right. If I'm too good, then they'll kill me,
但如果我做得太慢  那么我就会被处死
and if I'm too slow, then I'll die.
没错
Right.
祝你好运
Good luck.
祝你好运  翠丝
Good luck, Tris.
希望你能完成它
Hope you make it.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
四号
Whoa. Four!
快停下来
Stop! Four!
你不是无畏派的人吗
Aren't you Dauntless?
拜托告诉我你没看到那个场面
Please tell me that you weren't watching that.
如果我回答说没看到的话是不是会让你好受点
Would you feel better if I said no?
你做得很棒
You did well.
而现在
Now...
还有最后一项
One final test.
如果你想成为无畏派的一员
You know what to do.
什么
What?
你知道该怎么做
If you want to be Dauntless.
我不要
No.
来吧
Do it.
你没事吧
You all right?
对我来说你做得很不错  知道吗
That looked good to me, okay?
来吧  我们走
Come on. Let's go.
恭喜各位  同时也欢迎我们无畏派的新成员
Congratulations, new members of Dauntless.
无畏派! 无畏派! 无畏派!
Dauntless! Dauntless! Dauntless!
来这  排好队
Come on. Get in line.
好了各位  请排队
All right, everybody, line up.
怎么了
What's going on?
请所有无畏派的成员...
All Dauntless initiates,
向你们的领袖报道
report to your command leader.
好了  都听好了
All right, listen up!
在你们今晚离开之前  我想你们先排成四只队伍
Before you leave tonight, I want you all in four lines.
每个人都会得到一个追踪器
Everyone gets a tracking device.
不要有任何疑问  这只是预防措施而已
Don't ask questions. It's just a precaution.
你看见四号了吗
Do you see Four?
没有
No.
下一位
Next!
-这是怎么一回事    -我的天哪
- What's going on?  - Oh, my God.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你应该派第一只队伍的  但别担心...
You should be first in line, but...
那不会很疼的
I'll make it easy for you.
是不是被弄疼了  贱人
Hurts like a bitch, huh?
你现在终于成为我们的一员了
Now you're really one of us.
嘿  这是...
Hey, what's...
派系高于血缘
Faction before blood.
噢  我的天
Oh, my God.
他们现在可以看见和听见我们
They can see and hear us.
他们只是不以相同的方式来处理事情
They just don't process it the same way.
传感器会向他们传达命令
Commands come in through the transmitter.
这是怎么一回事
What's goin' on?
我们在干嘛
What are we doin'?
是分歧者
Divergent.
嘿
Hey!
这里一切都很好  你不用担心任何事情
Everything's fine. There's nothing to worry about.
快一点  快动起来
Hurry up! Move!
无私派的领袖必须认清楚他们自己
Abnegation leaders must identify themselves.
我想去找我的父母
We need to find my parents.
继续走吧  你的屋子在哪里
Just keep moving. Where's your house?
我们正在查找资料
We are looking for information.
所有的屋子都会被搜查
All houses will be searched.
没有反抗就没有流血
Do not resist. You will not be hurt.
妈? 爸?
Mom? Dad?
他们会去哪里
Where would they have gone?
我也不知道
I don't know.
这不可能发生在我们这  不要在这样了
This can't happen here! Just stop it!
不要反抗
Do not resist.
所有无私派的人都会被询查
All Abnegation will be questioned.
传说中的四号
The legendary Four...
只不过是一只没脑的工蜂而已
A mindless drone.
你曾经是在阶级里的第一名  而现在...
You were first in your class. Now you're...
一无所有
Nothing.
怎么了
What?
你觉得他是...
Think he might be...
有一个办法能够看出来
There's one way to find out.
说再见吧  混蛋
Say goodbye, asshole.
再见
Good bye.
再动的话我就开枪了
Move and you die!
无私派的呆子吗
The stiff?
看来现在有两个了
Two stiffs.
两个快挂掉的傻瓜
Two dead stiffs.
可不能让任何一条漏网之鱼逃掉
You can't let a single Divergent slip through.
而这就是放生他们的后果
This is what happens.
她是不会开枪的
She's not gonna shoot me.
我想你高估了我的性格了
Think you might be overestimating my character.
快跑
Run!
-你中弹了?     -嗯
- You were hit?  - Yeah.
他们在那  不要动
Right there! Don't move!
放下武器
Drop your weapons.
托比亚斯·伊顿
Tobias Eaton.
还有你  碧翠丝
And you, Beatrice.
我还以为是我的智慧让我感应到了你
I thought it was intellect I was sensing in you.
也许你没那么聪明
Maybe you're not as smart as you think you are.
为什么你要去攻击那些无辜的人们
Why are you attacking all these innocent people?
他们是无辜的吗
Innocent people?
倘若任由无私派发展  他们会破坏整个建制
Abnegation, if left unchecked, will destroy the faction system.
你们也同样是罪魁祸首
Same can be said of both of you.
必须有人阻止你们
Somebody has to stop you.
如果我们不出手  和平就不复存在
If we don't, peace will be lost.
和平早已不复存在了  是你亲手摧毁的
It's already been lost. You destroyed it.
是人性摧毁了它
Human nature destroyed it.
我们之中有远见的人会保护其他人
Those of us with the vision to see that are called upon to protect the rest.
我们会复原和平
We will restore the peace.
而这一次  它会继续维持下去
And this time, it will last.
但如果你是错的呢
And what if you're wrong?
把他带过来
Bring him with us.
她受伤了
She's injured.
她对我们一无是处
Any results would be unclear.
-你可以把她解决掉    -收到
- You can get rid of her.  - All right.
趴下
Get down!
我们走  快跟着
Let's go. Come on!
请支援部队到移动指挥部第五层报到
Additional security teams, report to mobile command Level 5.
碧翠丝!
Beatrice!
-妈?   妈!     -碧翠丝
- Mom? Mom!  - Beatrice.
好了
Okay.
好了  我们得赶紧离开
Okay, we gotta run!
你曾经是无畏派的一员
You were Dauntless.
今天保护我的任务就要落到你的头上了
Served me well today.
爸爸没事吧
Is Dad okay?
没事  他已经带领了整个团队到了门罗和斯泰特
Yeah. He led a group over to Monroe and State.
我们会在那跟他碰面
We're gonna meet him there.
我们走
Let's go!
他们在1区第9街
Copy 1-9!
威尔! 威尔!
Will! Will!
威尔!
Will!
威尔  快停下  快停下来
Will, stop! Stop!
快停下
Stop!
我...
I...
好了  亲爱的  我们得走了
Okay. Come on, honey. We gotta go.
是我把他杀了的  是我把他杀了的
I killed him. I killed him.
是我把他杀了
I killed him.
抱一下
Come here.
好了没事了
Okay.
我们得快点去找你爸爸
Let's go find your father.
-掩护我    -不要
- Cover me.  - No.
让我来
I'll go.
我们看见她了  长官
Got it, sir!
快跑! 快跑!
Don't stop! Don't stop!
我们走
Go!
-你没事吧?     -嗯  我还好
- You okay? Good.  - Yeah, I'm good.
好了我们走  现在没事了
Okay! Let's go! We're good.
妈妈?
Mom?
妈妈  你怎么了
Mom... What is it?
嘿...
Hey...
妈妈! 妈妈! 妈妈!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
妈妈!
Mom!
妈妈  不要!
Mom, no!
妈妈! 妈妈!
Mom! Mom!
能听到我说话吗? 妈妈!
Mom? Mom!
妈妈你快起来
Mom, wake up!
妈妈!
Mom!
我的天哪  妈妈
Oh, my God, Mom!
快停下! 停下!
Stop! Stop!
我爱你  妈妈
I love you, Mom...
噢我的天哪
Oh, my God!
我父亲在哪里
Where's my father?
碧翠丝?
Beatrice?
你的母亲呢
Your mother?
她救了我
She saved me.
她的努力没有白费
Then it wasn't in vain.
我们得离开这
We need to leave here.
外面还有士兵吗
Are there soldiers outside?
没有  很安全
No, it's clear.
我本应该相信你的
I should have believed you.
当我离开的时候我才意识到
I left as soon as I realized.
为什么会发生这一切  我不明白
Why is this happening? I don't understand.
为什么无畏派要与博学派发起战争
Why are Dauntless fighting for Erudite?
他们压根都不知道他们在做什么
They don't know what they're doing.
他们都被控制了
They're under simulation.
我们要把他们唤醒  我得回去无畏派
We need to wake 'em up. I need to get into Dauntless.
这太危险了
That's a fortress.
也不可能会发生
It's not gonna happen.
我可以让我们进里面去
I can get us in there.
准备好了
Get ready.
怎么了
What now?
我猜你不会喜欢的
You're not gonna like it.
这下面有一织网
There's a net at the bottom.
不要想太多  跳下去就行
Don't think, just jump.
你没事吧
Are you good?
都没事吧
Good?
我们走
Let's go.
先等等
Wait here.
靠在墙上
Against the wall.
Against the wall!
你怎么醒了
How are you awake?
因为我比你聪明
Because I'm smarter than you.
而且他们需要我
And they need me.
他们是在哪里控制人的
Where are they controlling it from?
为什么我要跟你说  你才不会开枪呢
Why would I tell you that? It's not like you're gonna shoot me.
为什么总有人这么说
Why do people keep saying that?
他们是在哪里控制人的
Where are they controlling it from?
我们真的要把他杀了吗
Did you really need to shoot him?
我们每浪费一分钟  就有一个无私派的人丧失性命
Every minute we waste, another Abnegation dies
而又有无畏派的一个人成为杀人凶手
and another Dauntless becomes a murderer.
彼得  我们走
Peter, let's go.
就这几个人  对吗
That's it, isn't it?
没错
Yeah.
我见过珍宁进去那里面
I've seen Jeanine go in there.
我觉得那就是她控制他们的地方
That's where she's controlling it from.
就如你所说  我们不能再浪费时间了
Like you said, there isn't a second to waste.
父亲  不要
Dad,no!
父亲
Dad...
嘿
Hey!
看好凯莱布  我要进去这里面
Watch Caleb. I'm going in there.
嘿  嗨
Hey. Hi.
四号
Four...
四号...  四号  是我  你是不是被控制了
Four... Four, it's me. You're in a sim.
他是听不见你讲话的
He can't hear you.
很神奇  对吧
Amazing, isn't it?
我们所知道构成思想的那些东西
Everything we think of that makes up a person,
思想  情感  还有经历
thoughts, emotions, history...
全都被化学给抹掉
All wiped away by chemistry.
四号
Four.
他已经不复存在了
He's gone.
我们都因为它而更安全
And we're all safer for it.
安全? 何以见得?
Safer? How are we safer?
派系系统的聪明之处在于
The brilliance of the faction system
其统一了各种派别
is that conformity to the faction removes the threat
消除了任何运用独立意志的人构成的威胁
of anyone exercising their independent will.
分歧者是建制的大患
Divergents threaten that system.
不要误会我的意思
Don't get me wrong.
你的反抗的确蕴含着一种美
There's a certain beauty in your resistance,
也就是你对分类的挑战
your defiance of categorization.
可这种美我们不能接受
But it's a beauty we can't afford.
四号  是我  是我啊
Four, it's me. It's me.
拜托了  四号  看着我  看着我
Please, Four, look at me. Look at me.
四号  是我
Four! It's me!
四号  快停下来
Four, stop!
快停下
Stop!
Stop...
四号...  拜托了...
Four... Please...
没事  没事  我爱你  这没关系
It's okay, it's okay. I love you. It's okay.
这没关系
It's okay.
我爱你  没关系的
I love you. It's okay.
四号  看着我  看着我
Four, look at me. Look at me.
是我  认得出来吗
It's me. It's me.
是我  是我
翠丝
Tris...
来吧
Go.
搞定他
Finish it.
救命
Help!
嘿
Hey!
把它关掉
Shut it down.
我不要
No.
我不会再问你一遍  快做!
I am not gonna ask you again. Do it!
把它  关掉
Shut it down!
我很佩服你愿意死在你所相信的人的面前
I admire you willing to die for what you believe...
我也一样
But so am I.
你做不了  不是吗
You can't do it, can you?
也许你不像真正的无畏派那样无畏
Maybe you're not quite as Dauntless as you thought you were.
没错
You're right.
我的确不适合无畏派
I'm not.
因为我是分歧者
I'm Divergent.
现在把系统关掉  然后清除程序
Now shut it down and wipe the program.
遥控停止
Simulation abort.
系统关闭
System-wide shutdown.
不要  这不可能
No... No...
不可能!
No!
不要误会我的意思
Don't get me wrong.
你的反抗的确蕴含着一种美
There's a certain beauty to your resistance.
翠丝...
Tris...
正在实行封锁
Lockdown now in effect.
好了  我们得赶紧行动
All right, let's move!
我们现在必须走了
We gotta go. Now.
托比亚斯
Tobias.
我们得赶紧离开这
We need to keep moving.
好了  走
All right, move!
儿子!
Son!
我自己能行的
I got it!
我知道你会的
I know you do.
我母亲和父亲昨天丧生了
My mom and dad died today.
他们都走了
They're gone.
我知道
I know.
可他们都爱你  翠丝
But they loved you, Tris.
对于他们来说  没有更好的方式来告诉你他们如何爱你
For them, there was no better way to show you.
我们现在一无所有
Now we have nothing.
我们没有家  也不再属于任何帮派
We have no home, no faction...
我甚至都不知道我自己是谁
I don't even know who I am anymore.
我对你了若指掌
I know exactly who you are.
你确定?
You sure about that?
是的  我非常确定
Yeah, I'm very sure.
来我这吧
Come here.
我们现在不再属于任何派系
We're like the Factionless now.
我们将一切都抛在身后
We've left everything behind,
但我们找回了彼此之间的信任
but we found ourselves and each other.
明天我们也许将再次战斗
Tomorrow we may have to fight again,
但现在  我们即将到达这条火车线的终点站
but, for now, we'll ride the train to the end of the line...
然后...
And then
我们将重新出发
we'll jump-
♪我不知道目的地何在  但我知道这将会是漫漫长路♪
♪And I don't know where I'm going But I know it's gonna be a long time♪
翻译:jyopon networmii timhal
校对:jyopon networmii timhal
♪因我于阳光散发着白酒苦味的早晨离去♪
♪And I'll be leaving in the morning Come the white wine bitter sunlight♪
后期:timhal
♪我想在今晚聆听你的心跳♪
♪Wanna hear your beating heart tonight♪
HDWinG字幕组原创翻译作品 转载请勿去掉后缀
♪在艳红的烈阳复苏之前♪
♪Before the bleeding sun comes alive♪
♪我会珍惜把握我仅有的♪
♪I want to make the best of what is left, hold tight♪
♪最后一次倾听我的心跳声♪
♪And hear my beating heart one last time♪
♪如今我无法面对已改变的一切♪
♪I can't face this now everything has changed♪
♪我只想陪在你身旁♪
♪I just wanna be by your side♪
♪擦出名为希望的火花♪
♪here's hoping we collide♪
♪我想在今晚聆听你的心跳♪
♪Wanna hear your beating heart tonight♪
♪在艳红的烈阳复苏之前♪
♪Before the bleeding sun comes alive♪
♪我会珍惜把握我仅有的♪
♪I want to make the best of what is left, hold tight♪
♪最后一次倾听我的心跳声♪
♪And hear my beating heart one last time♪
♪今晚想聆听你的心跳♪
♪Wanna hear your beating heart tonight♪